I hope you're ready to put your C++ skills the test.
皆さん C++の スキルを 試す準備は できたでしょうか
Let me reintroduce you to Andrei Vatavu from Mercedes-Benz.
もう一度 ご紹介しましょう Mercedes-Benzの Andrei Vatavuさんです
Hi, Andrei, thank you for having us.
Andrei どうぞよろしく
&gt;&gt; Hi, David.
&gt;&gt; こちらこそ
&gt;&gt; So at this point student should have a pretty good intuition of the concepts
&gt;&gt; この時点で 学生たちは カルマンフィルターの 背後にある コンセプトを
behind Kalman filters.
よく 理解できているはずです
What do you want them to do in this lesson?
このレッスンでは どんな内容を 予定していますか?
&gt;&gt; Good question.
&gt;&gt; よく 聞いてくれました
In this lesson,
このレッスンでは
you will learn how to develop a fusion system by using Kalman filters.
カルマンフィルターを 使って フュージョンシステムを 開発する方法を 学びます
As David said,
Davidの 言うとおり
after the lesson with Sebastian, you should already have a good sense of
Sebastianのレッスンを受けた 皆さんは 推定問題に カルマンフィルターを
how to generally apply the Kalman filter to estimation problems.
適用する方法を 理解しているはずです
You've only used it to combine sequential measurements from one sensor.
1つのセンサーから 得た 一連の 測定値を 組み合わせるのに 使いましたね
But actually, it's also possible to use Kalman filters to combine measurements
でも 実は カルマンフィルターを使って 異なるセンサーから 得た 測定値を
from different sensors.
組み合わせることも できます
And that's why we use it in sensor fusion.
だからこそ センサーフュージョンに 使えるのです
&gt;&gt; That sounds pretty neat.
&gt;&gt; それは すばらしいですね
The plan for the project in this module is to use sensor fusion to track
このモジュールで行う プロジェクトは センサーフュージョンを 使った
a pedestrian, right?
歩行者の追跡ですよね?
&gt;&gt; Right, you have already learned that lidar and
&gt;&gt; そうです LiDARと レーダーには それぞれ
radar have their individual strengths and weaknesses.
長所と 短所が あることを 学びましたね
By combining the strengths of both of these sensors,
そこで この2つの センサーの 長所を 組み合わせれば
you'll be able to estimate precisely the pedestrian location, heading, and speed.
歩行者の 位置や方向 速度を 正確に推定できるように なります
And one last thing, you will implement all of this in C++.
もう 1つ 大事なのは C++で 実行するという 点です